{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Interior Painters","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40118/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40118,"taskName":"Interior Home or Surfaces - Paint or Stain","taskDescription":"Paint or Stain Interior Surfaces","xmTaskDescriptor":"Interior Painters","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":125,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"decorative fireplace Stain paint doors","textMessagingName":"Paint Interior","rolloverLongDesc":"Interior painting of whole rooms, walls, ceilings, trim etc. Painters generally also handle all relevant prep work including washing, scraping, sanding, caulking, patching \u0026 priming. Note separate categories for faux finishes, textured paint, murals, electrostatic painting, refinishing furniture \u0026 popcorn finishes.","rolloverShortDesc":"Interiror painting of whole rooms, hallways, walls, ceilings etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Paint, Varnish or Stain Interior Surfaces.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Interior Painting \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Interior Painters - HomeAdvisor","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":55,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":40365,"bridgeTaskText":"Got a small painting project? ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"Submit a small painting project request","bridgeTaskLinkId":15027,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Interior Home Paint or Stain","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Interior Home or Surfaces - Paint or Stain","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Interior Home Painting Project","urlName":"Interior-Home-or-Surfaces-Paint-or-Stain","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Interior Painting Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"decorative,Stain,paint,doors,repaint,bedroom,painting,painter, bathroom, kitchen, varnish","emcCategoryOid":-12054,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":429,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40118/":{"taskOID":40118,"originalTaskOID":40118,"setID":429,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500844,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Rooms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms or areas need to be painted?","shortQuestionText":"How many rooms or areas need to be painted?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10933,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203106,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 4","answerDisplayText":"3 - 4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203107,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 6","answerDisplayText":"5 - 6","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203164,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"7 - 8","answerDisplayText":"7 - 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201009,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"9 or more","answerDisplayText":"9 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5235,"questionDisplayText":"House Occupancy","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the occupancy of the house?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2686,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Furnished and occupied","answerDisplayText":"Furnished and occupied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Furnished and unoccupied","answerDisplayText":"Furnished and unoccupied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2207,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Empty of furnishings and unoccupied","answerDisplayText":"Empty of furnishings and unoccupied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":551,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms to be Painted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which rooms need to be painted? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6955,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Whole house","answerDisplayText":"Whole house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3625,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Living areas","answerDisplayText":"Living areas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2911,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hallways","answerDisplayText":"Hallways","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6029,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stairways","answerDisplayText":"Stairways","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500845,"questionDisplayText":"Painting Needs:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be painted?","shortQuestionText":"What needs to be painted?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9512,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walls and ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Walls and ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1305,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500844,"questionDisplayText":"Number of Rooms","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many rooms or areas need to be painted?","shortQuestionText":"How many rooms or areas need to be painted?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10933,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203106,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 4","answerDisplayText":"3 - 4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203107,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 6","answerDisplayText":"5 - 6","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203164,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"7 - 8","answerDisplayText":"7 - 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201009,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"9 or more","answerDisplayText":"9 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10933,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203106,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 4","answerDisplayText":"3 - 4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203107,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 6","answerDisplayText":"5 - 6","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203164,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"7 - 8","answerDisplayText":"7 - 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201009,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"9 or more","answerDisplayText":"9 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5235,"questionDisplayText":"House Occupancy","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the occupancy of the house?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2686,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Furnished and occupied","answerDisplayText":"Furnished and occupied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Furnished and unoccupied","answerDisplayText":"Furnished and unoccupied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2207,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Empty of furnishings and unoccupied","answerDisplayText":"Empty of furnishings and unoccupied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2686,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Furnished and occupied","answerDisplayText":"Furnished and occupied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Furnished and unoccupied","answerDisplayText":"Furnished and unoccupied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2207,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Empty of furnishings and unoccupied","answerDisplayText":"Empty of furnishings and unoccupied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":551,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms to be Painted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which rooms need to be painted? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6955,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Whole house","answerDisplayText":"Whole house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3625,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Living areas","answerDisplayText":"Living areas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2911,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hallways","answerDisplayText":"Hallways","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6029,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stairways","answerDisplayText":"Stairways","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6955,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Whole house","answerDisplayText":"Whole house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3625,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Living areas","answerDisplayText":"Living areas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2911,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Hallways","answerDisplayText":"Hallways","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6029,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Stairways","answerDisplayText":"Stairways","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500845,"questionDisplayText":"Painting Needs:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be painted?","shortQuestionText":"What needs to be painted?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9512,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walls and ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Walls and ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1305,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6774,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Walls","answerDisplayText":"Walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9512,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walls and ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Walls and ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1305,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Ceilings","answerDisplayText":"Ceilings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}